RAÚL ICHIRO ROSAS CHINEN

COMPUTER SCIENCE AND INFORMATICS STUDENT

(+51) 933-452-921

ichiro.rosass@gmail.com

My LinkedInMy GitHub

ABOUT ME

Outstanding Peruvian Computer Science and Informatics student at the Cibertec Institute (Peru), where I have achieved the 3rd and 2nd positions in the first and second study cycles respectively. I aim to specialize in and to perform at the Backend development area. I am known for my organizational skills, willingness to learn, and my hobbies are music, video games, and exploring new income streams.

SKILLS AND ABILITIES

Responsible, perseverant, and outgoing.

Ability to work both independently and as part of a team. Language proficiency: Native Spanish, advanced English, and basic Japanese.

EDUCATION

2016-2022| UNIVERSIDAD PERUANA DE CIENCIAS APLICADAS (UPC) | LIMA, PERU

Music degree (completed coursework up to the 7th cycle)

2023-PRESENT | CIBERTEC INSTITUTE | LIMA, PERU

Degree in Computer Science and Informatics. Currently in the 3rd cycle of the program (2024-I)

TECHNICAL SKILL SET

Java, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, SQL (basic) and Microsoft SQL Server (basic).

RELEVANT PROJECTS (GITHUB)

Sales software for a store (October 2023 - December 2023):

Final Project at Cibertec for the Algorithms and Data Structures (AED - 2nd cycle) course.

It features a simple database in Notepad.

I served as coordinator and group leader for the development of this software, as well as the main software developer, using and acquiring new knowledge in lava

Website about the FIFA World Cups won by the Argentina national football team (October 2023 - December 2023):

Final Project at Cibertec for the Web Environment Development (DEW - 2nd cycle) course.

It includes various transitions made with JavaScript.

I contributed to the development of the website using my knowledge of HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.

COURSES AND CERTIFICATIONS

Máster Completo en Java de cero a experto 2024 (+127 hrs) | UDEMY Platform STATUS: Currently in progress

EXPERIENCE

2019 - 2021 | MUSIC TEACHER | DOREMI SCHOOL

Taught guitar and piano classes.

APRIL - NOVEMBER 2022 | SOUND ASSISTANT | REAL CLUB DE LIMA

Managed sound equipment at the Real Club de Lima for its weekly events under the supervision of a sound technician.

2022 - PRESENT | OFFICE SUPPLY STORE | FAMILY BUSINESS

Customer service, cash handling, and inventory management.